http://www.jumpymonkey.com/pages/privacy-policy

Enjoy Free Shipping on Orders of $51 or more (Excluding fundraisers).
Ships to the Contiguous 48 states.
Special arrangements need to be made for Hawaii and Alaska!
×
Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy Policy
Jumpy Monkey Coffee Roasting Co.
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
Jumpy Monkey Coffee Roasting Co. will not intentionally disclose any personally identifying information about you (including information obtained by the Site from cookies and information regarding your IP address) to third parties without your consent except where Jumpy Monkey Coffee Roasting Co., in good faith, believes such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or to enforce these Terms and Conditions of the Site.
Jumpy Monkey Coffee Roasting Co. reserves the right to collect general demographic and other market information that does not personally identify you to any person without additional consent.  We utilize e-mails to notify you for sales purposes, to let you know of special promotions, events and policy changes.
New customers are automatically opted-in to receive Jumpy Monkey Coffee's email, promotional marketing e-mails, promotional partner e-mails, newsletters, fairness e-mails or announcement (i.e. site enhancement) e-mails.
CONTACT US
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or how we collect and use the information of our customers, you can contact us by emailing us at info1@jumpymonkey.com.
306 1st Street, Suite 1
Sergeant Bluff, IA 51054712-943-3026info1@jumpymonkey.com
Quick Links
HomeShopSearchContact
Information
FundraisingDistributorsPrivacy PolicyShipping & ReturnsTerms of Service
Newsletter
Subscribe to our mailing list:
OK
Copyright © 2020, Jumpy Monkey® Coffee.
All Rights Reserved.
0
